# Ken Eucker

Email: Private

Address: Portland, Oregon

Website: www.linkedin.com/in/keneucker





#### **SUMMARY**

I am a full stack developer, classically trained in object oriented programming, who likes to write universal javascript, with extensive experience building the backend of web connected properties. I have a diverse set of skills writing in the serverside languages C#, PHP, Javascript, and the clientside languages HTML, Javascript, CSS, JSX, including the database languages mysql, MSSQL, and Mongodb.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Clevertech Oct 2019 - Present6 months

Senior Node Developer

Ken Eucker LLC

Jan 2019 - Present 1 year 3 months

Contract Software Engineer

Uncorked Studios

Apr 2019 - Jun 20193 months

Full Stack Developer

Digital Trends

Feb 2017 - Dec 20181 year 11 months

Web Developer

Seven Twenty Studios LLC

Jun 2011 - Jan 20175 years 8 months

Freelance Software Engineer

Solid Interactive

Mar 2016 - Dec 201610 months

Web Developer

RWest

Mar 2014 - Apr 20151 year 2 months

Contract Web Developer

Viewpoint Construction Software

Dec 2011 - Jan 20142 years 2 months

Software Development Engineer

Overland Agency

May 2010 - Jul 20111 year 3 months

Software Developer I

### **EDUCATION**

## Oregon Institute of Technology

2006 - 2010

Bachelors of Science

### **VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCE & CAUSES**

# Black Rock Ranger

Burning Man Project

Cultural Ambassador

May 2014 - May 20162 years 1 month

CASCADIANOW

Aug 2019 - Present8 months

#### **PROJECTS**

## github.com/KenEucker/quasar

Nov 2017 - Jan 2019

A light version of the quasi app runtime that uses simple web files to generate a single html output.

Intended to be used with small purpose html snippets and single paged websites, supporting only a single html, css, and js file for input.

This project was created for the automation of ad units at Digital Trends and is a continuation of previous projects I had started for personal reasons. Quasi was started last year around this time and serves a very similar function to this project. Quasi, however, has many many more features that make it more complicated to use. quasar is clearly a step in the right direction with simplicity and a lack of scope creep.

A light version of the quasi app runtime that uses simple web files to generate a single html output. Intended to be used with small purpose html snippets and single paged websites, supporting only a single html, css, and js file for input.

This project was created for the automation of ad units at Digital Trends and is a continuation of previous projects I had started for personal reasons. Quasi was started last year around this time and serves a very similar function to this project....

A light version of the quasi app runtime that uses simple web files to generate a single html output. Intended to be used with small purpose html snippets and single paged websites, supporting only a single html, css, and js file for input.

This project was created for the automation of ad units at Digital Trends and is a continuation of previous projects I had started for personal reasons. Quasi was started last year around this time and serves a very similar function to this project. Quasi, however, has many many more features that make it more complicated to use. quasar is clearly a step in the right direction with simplicity and a lack of scope creep.

# github.com/KenEucker/quasi

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

an express based framework intended to provide all of the features you would need to run a simple webserver from simple configuration files that inform the app how it should serve your html pages, using a DOM structure based templating engine that enables developers to create their templates without a tightly coupled content management system an express based framework intended to provide all of the features you would need to run a simple webserver from simple configuration files that inform the app how it should serve your html pages, using a DOM structure based templating engine that enables developers to create their templates without a tightly coupled content management system

# github.com/KenEucker/wpbuilder

Oct 2014 - Jun 2015

A wordpress plugin building framework that incorporates other open source projects to provide a sandbox for wordpress plugin development and deployment.

A wordpress plugin building framework that incorporates other open source projects to provide a sandbox for wordpress plugin development and deployment.